

M Lutfhi Aditya Putra

Jakarta, Indonesia • +6282124544334 • mluthfiaditya1@gmail.com

PROFILE

My name M Luthfi Aditya Putra, 22 years old, a fresh graduate from bachelor of Computer Science at Bina Nusantara University specialization Database System. I learned about C, C++, C#, Java, Javascript and SQL. Currently I am looking for a position to work professionally. Very motivated to be a personality that can be useful for the progress of the industry and grow professionally. I am confident in my abilities that will produce promising benefits. I would relish the opportunity to apply from what I have learned so far at university but also interest to learn new things.

EDUCATION

Bina Nusantara University

Jakarta, Indonesia

Computer Science 2018 – 2022

GPA: 3.21/4.00

WORK EXPERIENCE

PT Graha Technosoft Informatika

Feb 2022 – Now

Technical Consultant Employee

- Develop custom business process on Dynamic CRM using Plugin, Workflow and Javascript.
- Develop SSRS Report to Summarize the most demanding data. Enabling data logic inside rdl Report by using XML Query, direct SQL Query, and SQL Store Procedure.
- Analyze and tune performance SQL Query and other logic algorithm such as plugin, HTML, and Javascript code.
- Develop SQL Query to analyze missing data, data relation, and support backend business process development.
- Develop external and internal microservices to satisfy data integration cross platform using .Net web service.
- Familiar with several SDLC such as Waterfall, Agile, etc.
- Develop Store Procedure to retrieve data from other stored Databse using Scheduled Job SQL Agent
- Develop SSIS package using C# Language for retrieve data from JSON API.

PT Graha Technosoft Informatika

Feb 2021 – Feb 2022

Technical Consultant Intern

- Develop Report Dashboard HTML to emphasize complex data visualization.
- Debug and Fixing Reported Issue on Dynamic CRM.
- Providing support to ensure Go-Live as planned.
- Develop UI Automation to facilitate the work of the Support Team using EasyRepro and Gherkin Language

Circle Place Coffee Shop

Mar 2020 - Feb 2021

Founder of Circle Place Coffee Shop

- Ensured that cleanliness standards were upheld.
- Handled any customer service complaints.
- Tracked daily revenue and prepared related weekly and monthly reports.
- Remained on-site for required food safety and cleanliness inspections.
- Train all new hires on the essential elements of coffee shop work, including customer service, machine operation, and food safety guidelines.

PT Sumidhaz Permata Bunda

Jan 2016 - Feb 2017

Network Technician

- Install and Improve internet network for customers
- Install and repair pointing device to increase network speed
- Install router and configure IP for new customer

PT KIE INDONESIA Apr 2015 – Jan 2016

Teaching Assistant

- Teaching mathematics to students of PT KIE INDONESIA
- Check student answer also guide students to answer correctly.

ACHIEVEMENTS

Mathematics Contest	2016
1st Place Mathematics Contest in PEKANBARU	
Swimming Competition	2015

1st Place Swimming Competition in RIAU

Swimming Competition 2015

1st Place Swimming competition in PEKANBARU

SKILLS

Programming : C,C++, C#, Java, Javascript, HTML, PHP, MySQL, CISCO, ReactJS.

Soft Skill: Problem Solving, Critical Thinking, Communication, Time Management, and Teamwork.

Interest: Programming, Networking.

Language: Indonesian (Native), English (TOEFL 540).